Baby
I
I have a favor to ask.
We just
Mr. Seonmin, work
Let’s pretend not to know
How much does this mean to you?
I don't know if it's painful
But
I am this company
How did you come in?
You know that too
And above all
Our Minwoo and Minjun are our parents.
I feel sorry for other people's injustice, but
I want to protect my family
It's the most important
So
for my family
this thing
Can't I just take my hands off it?
yes
Then
Actually, I don't think that's true either
I was thinking
And you had a hard time holding on
avoid you
I don't even want to do it
I'm so sorry
Baby, I'm sorry
Oh no, no
I'm more sorry
This kind of thing bothers me for no reason.
sleep
Because I have another morning broadcast tomorrow
I have to leave early
Come in quickly
You had a hard time holding on
avoid you
I don't even want to do it
Why is my heart so heavy?
Mom, I want to play with Yun Kwon
Can we go hang out with Yoon Kwon?
Yoon Kwon?
Who is Yoon Kwon?
Sunshine Half Kim Yun-kwon
Uh, it's not the same class, it's the class next to it.
Uh, with Yoon Kwon.
I played the day before and the day before that too.
I also played the day before the war.
Yoon Kwon is very strong.
There are a lot of toys too.
Even when playing at the playground
all my friends
He wants to play tag with Yun Kwon.
Can I go hang out with Yun Kwon?
Our Minwoo is Yoon Kwon
I guess they really like it
If you want to hang out at Yoon Kwon’s
We met Yoon Kwon first.
After inviting
Shall we go hang out with Yun Kwon?
Mom will ask the teacher
Wow, this is exciting!
our princes
Have fun today too!
yes
hello
yes, teacher
I... Minwoo's mother...
I have something to tell you.
Are you coming home from work?
Can you stop by for a moment?
Kids, catch me
Yes? Minwoo is a witness?
Earlier, during free play time
playing with clay
Yoon Kwon, Minwoo, Sora
Um... I went to the bathroom to wash my hands.
I heard crying and went there.
Oh my! What should I do?
Look, teacher.
Oh my, what should I do!
Whew!
Guys, what happened?
He suddenly slipped
Sora said
Yoon Kwon pushed him to the floor.
They said he hit his head.
But Yoon Kwon and Min Woo
Sora slipped and fell alone
They said it was a collision
Minwoo
Earlier in the bathroom
Did Yoon Kwon push Sora?
no
You can just tell the teacher
Because I’m suspicious, it’s just Minwoo.
I called him separately and asked.
Minwoo also says that Yoonkwon is right.
Sora is lying
I did
Anyway, the only thing I saw
Because Minwoo said no
I passed it for now...
Our Minwoo
Mom will ask me just once
Our Minwoo is like a lie
Because I believe that he is the one who doesn't do it.
Mom will only ask once
Our Minwoo
Yoon Kwon pushing Sora
Did you see it? Didn't you see it?
No, it wasn't Yun Kwon who pushed it.
Sora slipped and
I hit my head
Really?
Did Sora slip alone?
Isn’t it Yoon Kwon who pushed it?
No, no!
They say no
Why do teachers and mom keep asking questions?
Okay, okay.
Our Minwoo
Because I'm not a liar
Because he is an honest and good person
Right?
Mom is
We believe in Minwoo
go and play
Ah, teacher
I just asked Minwoo.
It's not that Yoon Kwon pushed Sora.
I think Sora was a bit mistaken.
Hey, what are you doing, Illy?
No, Sang-gyu and I
It's a day off
Going for a picnic
Just packing a lunch box
Oh, I'm crazy about what this is.
I'm out of my mind
Uh, I packed yours too, here.
Hey, is this simple?
If anyone sees it, I'm selling lunch boxes.
I thought I was leaving.
That's right
Why are the ingredients like this?
Don't you know if they sell a lot?
oh my god!
- Hey, did you do all this?
- hey!
you eat that one
This is now blatantly discriminatory.
Illy, why have you changed like this?
Do you like Sang-gyu that much?
what?
I don't have anyone to meet right now
We're just meeting
If I don’t think so, I’ll quit at any time.
Damn, shit
I have to send it to Sang-gyu.
- How excited are you?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, no!
Hey, no, come here!
You come here, hey!
Please save me!
Hey, delete it!
- Delete, did I say?
- Wrong, ugh!
What?
Why are you talking about that now?
No, that...
Not really
It wasn't important
Oh, and nothing
It seemed like there was no sense, so I just
I was trying to get over it, but...
Is it okay if I don't feel anything?
The quiet one is more suspicious, right?
Then, when Jo Na-jeong finds out
If you get upset and a problem arises,
How are you going to fix that?
How much did we talk about?
no
With Now Won-bin
With Kim Seon-min
I was asked if it was true that we were dating.
I just said I heard it before.
I said I didn't know the exact details.
action
If you can't do it right
At least say something immediately!
Why can’t I do anything right?
go out
Did you call me?
uh
sit down
Chi... just
How is work life, are there any difficulties?
I asked to see it because I was curious.
Still I
He was a nice subordinate.
I feel like I didn't take care of it too much
Thanks for your hard work
I'm having fun working
Yes!
much more than you think
I feel good because I'm doing well.
They also ask for magazine interviews
Uh, it also prevents punctures.
Do you feel excited about your future activities?
If you think about it,
You came here thanks to me
You used to go to
When a marketing company launches a car
The announcer had a funk
Watching society
If I host your show
Just because I thought I would do well
Didn’t you take the entrance exam?
Oh, right
Thanks to the managing director, I became a show host.
I was up for the challenge, yes.
Now that I think about it, I
I am a very special benefactor to you.
Right?
I'm really grateful
no, what
I'm not saying that it's my job to do public affairs.
I care about you especially
There is a reason why I can't help but believe this.
It's like this
The truth is, Najeong.
These days I'm so
Because I'm lonely
You too, a little more
As you get older, you will feel it.
It's so hard to survive as a working mom.
It's not easy
No matter how much college you went to
My daughter is still immature
The person called husband
You know, not on my side.
I'm on someone else's side
Ha...
us
Not a boss-employee relationship
As a working mom friend
let's go for a long time
Just do it like this, just do it like this
Don't just have random accidents
Then
The person who signs the contract last
Because you will be
Do you understand?
Yes, I will work hard.
Uh, baby
Yes, father
I finished the meeting early today.
I'll pick up the kids.
Yes, rest.
yes
"Sweet"
Hey, how are you so pretty?
Have you thought about packing a lunch?
I just woke up early for the first time in a while.
I made it roughly with things I had at home.
- Because I don’t want to buy it.
- Hey
I'm falling in love with Illy again like this
Huh?
Why do you look so pretty today?
It's not my fault
fact
That's right, fact
Elijah, Elijah, wait...
Wow, I almost got in big trouble.
You are truly perfect!
What is it? What about this natural skinship?
What are you talking about?
Skinship?
let's go
I guess you've been in a relationship
at the age of forty
If you've never been in a relationship
Well, what's even weirder is that the child
Actually
So
How many people have you dated?
If it comes out like this
If I pass by
I don't think this will work
Oh my?
I'm so stuck
Does it look like a human?
tell me
How many people have you dated?
not much
Well, anyway
What, one or three people?
What?
How many people are there?
So
How long have you been dating?
The two met briefly
I met one person a little longer than that.
Oh, so how much?
3 years?
Wow
Better than I thought, bro
He was the noble and gentle type.
What was he doing?
A doctor who worked at the same hospital
Wow, that was a good job.
But why on earth did they break up?
A man and a woman break up
Could there be just one reason?
Well, many things...
Are you offended?
Hey, maybe you
Are you jealous now?
what?
Why me?
Why like this?
That's right, jealous, huh?
and!
It's really delicious, really, huh?
Hey, Illy, you're real
Ira just has a pretty face
You're good at cooking too, huh?
Hey, why aren't you eating?
Are you on a diet?
I said kid, huh?
You don't have any weight to lose
Was she a good cook too?
uh?
No, think about it.
If you've been seeing each other for 3 years, even if you pack a lunch box for me
I would have given you a hundred times.
I'm getting married too
It must have been discussed a hundred times.
I'm just curious
Are you good at cooking or not?
Aida, I couldn't even cook a single dish.
If you just did it, I would have done it all.
Wow
Cooking too
Just do it
Did you do that?
I guess I really liked it
But why did they break up?
Still haven’t forgotten?
- That, that, that, that, that's not that.
- Huh?
- My, my words
-Why...
Why do you stutter?
Did you hit the nail on the head?
No, but
Are you really coming? uh?
If you are in your forties and have no experience
That's more burdensome
You told me to take it easy
I told you everything
If it comes out like this
- What should I do?
- Chi!
Then stop pretending to be so innocent.
Why did you make people excited and now...
They say they haven’t forgotten me for a long time!
He said I was his first love!
Sleep, wait a minute...
Elijah, Elijah!
Elijah, wait a minute.
Oh! Ah, Elijah.
I'm in big trouble
Hey, we're in big trouble. Wait a minute.
Oh, how embarrassing!
Why did you do that? Sneaky!
why! why! why!
ah! I'm really annoyed
Ah, Mr.
- I'm back, grandpa!
- Grandpa!
- I've been there.
- Uh, yeah.
Oh my, you idiots
To the point where I sweat like this
Did you play?
Quickly take off your clothes and take a bath.
No, leave it, I'll wash it.
No
Hungry Tindy
You should quickly wash up and eat too.
I cooked soybean paste stew deliciously.
Thank you, father.
Okay, come on, let’s go take a shower.
Ahhh
Minwoo Noh
Who gave you this pippo pippo?
A friend gave it to me
Who are your friends?
My friend gave it to me but I can't say it
Your friend gave it to you, right?
brought from kindergarten
Isn't it a toy?
No, it's not a kindergarten toy.
A friend gave it to me!
So
A friend gave it to me
Why can't you speak?
Yoon Kwon...
Yoon Kwon?
Why did Yoon Kwon give this to you?
Just...
Honestly, don't you say anything?
Yoon Kwon suddenly
Why did I give this to you?
You can't believe it...
Then that
Did you lie to your mom?
I'm sorry mom
At that time, Yoon Kwon...
Ah!
push the conch
Sora got hit on the head.
Because I'm trying to tell the teacher
I gave it to you and told you not to tell me.
Because I’m Yun Kwon’s friend
Not Sora's friend...
Because Yoon Kwon is my friend
I gave it to you and told you not to tell me.
how do you
How could you lie like that?
My friend got hurt!
Because you lied
My friend didn't even get an apology
You've become a liar!
How could you do that
Can you do it? how?
mom
i was wrong
I was wrong
Because no one saw Yun Kwon.
They said it was okay if I didn't say anything.
They said it was okay if we just didn't talk.
Even if no one else knows
you know
Mom read the book with a conscience!
Because you lied like that
- Can you become a great person?
- Mom
I was wrong
Baby, I'm here
no
Why are you doing this?
Baby
Yeah
just us
Seonmin, work
Let’s file a complaint with the ethics committee.
Why?
What happened?
Actually, Minwoo
A few days ago at kindergarten
Even after seeing my friend hit another kid
I fell for one toy
To the teacher and to me
I lied casually
so today
After scolding Minwoo, I thought about it.
Seonmin, work
If you just close your eyes like this
I become the same as Minwoo.
What qualifications do I have?
Teach kids?
By what qualifications...
Hey
Then
Your husband or my husband
I couldn’t say more because I was a family member.
something
Could it be possible?
Were you surprised that I asked you to meet me like this?
no
Me too
Problems only with them
I don't think I should leave it to you
I was going to ask you to meet me sometime.
Well then, let’s talk now.
Why on earth are you trying to get a divorce?
It's still like that, how can you
Without even consulting adults
You guys do it together
Do you get a divorce stamp?
sorry
no, no
You can do that when you're young
Well...
When I was young, Wook supported me
I want to finish it all and I can
But every time that happens, if you get divorced
The couple who will remain in Korea
How many?
Mom, I told you
Not Jooyoung.
I asked for a divorce
Why did you ask Jooyoung?
Are you still like that?
Because Jooyoung also agreed
You wouldn't have divorced!
An innocent guy like you
You took the lead
There was no way they got divorced.
Ah, I
Not having children
Did you decide to nag me once?
Did you decide to pay attention?
Be careful with other people
I said I'd be careful
After experiencing this kind of misfortune,
It's so absurd
I'm really shocked
master
Let's listen, let's listen
What you are saying is strange.
Then the master and wife
They didn't have children
It's my child's fault
Did you think about it?
The divorce was also because of Jooyoung.
What do you think?
- No, I mean...
- To put it bluntly,
The reason is 100% fault.
Oh, isn’t it from the West?
What do you mean by that now?
That's right
Oh, the West only has that perverted hobby.
Even if I didn't have it
Do you think it would have happened like this?
Mom, why are you like this?
Stop it!
You're talking about adults
Don't step out, stay still
master
Master's wife
Oh, the West is with a human-sized doll
Talk and take pictures
What our Jooyoung did after seeing the scars
Did you know?
Didn't you know?
Before
Oh, I heard Seobu likes dolls.
It's just what young people do these days
I thought it was a kidult or something.
But
How to replace people
Do you like dolls?
I'm that doll too
I looked at the head and thought it was the flagship.
What must he have done?
Because I like that kind of thing
That's why I didn't have a child
How is that his fault?
Mom, why are you like this? without courtesy
Get out now!
Let's go out now
- Quick!
- Oh, why is he like this?
Don't you let go of this?
who now
Are you treating me like a pervert?
Without even knowing!
those dolls
What the master thinks
They're not those weird dolls.
Those dolls...
When he was young!
Mom, stop stop stop!
Why, what did I do wrong?
Shouldn’t you say what you have to say?
Stop it!
Are you doing this because you want to see me die?
why? Why...
Still, this is unfair
We need to talk!
- why!
- I'm sorry.
What on earth is this?
Where did you get slapped?
Are you mad at your mom?
How can you say something like that?
In front of Sangmin and your mother?
How hurtful that would be
Can't you guess?
What about mom?
Then the responsibility for divorce
You say it as if it's all on you
Are you just listening like a fool?
So why bother with a child over 40?
Are you saying let go of the boat?
- I take care of my own business!
- under!
Whether you are forty, fifty, or sixty
you are to me
You will always be a sad child.
Could it go wrong?
I'm worried that I'll get hurt!
To that kind of mother
Is that what you mean?
yes
Mom, you care about me and save me
I always felt grateful.
So Minyoung
Even when you go astray
Because I don’t want to upset my mother
Mom
I didn't do anything I didn't like.
But until when?
I also have to live my life
How long will you live as a good daughter to your mother?
Can you just let me go now?
Are you saying this so that I can live well?
I wish you all the best!
Whether I do well or not!
Either ruin your life or ruin it!
It's all mine and my share.
It's not mom's!
cadet! Ah...
Yes?
Director Kim Jeong-sik?
Yes...
This is the ethics committee at our headquarters.
For what reason?
Sexual harassment?
How can this be so ridiculous?
Are you framing me?
What a person of integrity I am
Are you making such an absurd slander?
So this is how it happened
That friend named Kim Seon-min
I was so bad at work
There are no sales
No complaints from partners
I, by name and name, am the head of the headquarters.
Can you just watch?
We had no choice but to exclude it from the program.
I also asked for your understanding
Then this friend
It's about to hit you with your body!
So I spoke firmly.
‘Seonmin, you can’t live like this.’
Then this friend
Let alone reflection
Holding a grudge
Bring No PD with you
Why are you demanding an apology from me?
then
Why did you send this message?
Boss to subordinate
Can’t you even ask for a meal?
yes?
And hanging underneath it
They said it was excluded from the programming.
I was so angry that he left.
I meant it to appease you.
So, what about this article?
Even if that’s not Kim Seon-min
Anyone who wants to
Can't you use it?
It's 100% manipulation.
Then
What about this?
About the part where I was molested
It was stated quite specifically.
How do you believe this?
Go to a psychiatrist
If you say I was molested
I'm giving you a consultation letter.
Can't you do it anywhere?
Ha...
What happened?
Hey, it looks like you don't believe me.
And this kid
where did you get it
Kim Seon-min's psychiatric counseling paper
They're pushing it in
What are you doing this for?
Yeah...
It's nothing else
What happened with you and the general manager?
Have we ever talked about it before?
yes
Wonbin or Najeong
Have you ever been approached?
yes, none
Yeah yeah
Thank goodness
No, it's Wonbin now.
I got caught up in the mentality of a hero for no reason.
Seonmin’s problem was needlessly raised
I feel like I'm wandering around
If you get caught up in it too
You're not the only one losing money
Our entire suite
It could get dangerous
The industry is already difficult.
Why are you acting so thoughtlessly?
Oh my, this pain in my head is killing me.
honestly
While working at work
Men's thoughtless actions
If you act sensitive
Only women get tired
you know
The manager, that person
I have a bad drinking habit, but tsk
I didn't do it on purpose.
Because my personality is so innocent,
If you like it
It's a temperament I can't hide.
Oh no
Oh, by the way, you
The reason I said I wanted to change to fashion was
Is it still the same?
11 o'clock this time
Prime time corner
I keep getting pushed out by other channels
I'm thinking of reorganizing it.
Once in fashion
How about giving it a try?
i
Should I make a suggestion to the programming team?
Kim Seon-min is the show host.
To me
With myself and Noh PD
I like you
So I confessed that it was difficult.
So
I said that wasn't right
I tried to stop him but...
After...
Actually, from long ago
The relationship between the two is strange
Rumors abounded.
Oh, think about it, okay?
No, the wrong person instead
The accusation itself
Isn't it suspicious?
Because rumors of an affair spread
This was done to cover it up.
As a human molester
Driving, shit, tsk
no
absolutely not true
I told you
We met to help
It was distorted.
No, but do it like this
What if I distort it?
I'll hold off for a moment
On hold?
no, what
Are we just going to cover it up?
Unless the person involved is unconscious
In order to clearly determine the facts
We also have limits
Both sides of the argument are so tense
It's easy for us too
It's difficult to make decisions
No, where is that?
I even take the disadvantages
Now it's all the way to the ethics committee.
We are the accusers
Because the protection provisions are being followed
Don't worry too much
After discussing the rest some more
I'll say it again
Why on earth is Yena like that?
Actually...
Yena is a victim too
What?
Victim?
So with Seonmin
I persuaded him to file a complaint.
They stubbornly said no
That never happened
It's my opinion
Rather, those people
Using that as a weakness
Do whatever you want with Yena
I feel like I'm swinging
I resented you a lot, right?
I'm sorry
But I was so scared
Then I'm afraid I'll be buried in the industry.
Ha...
How can that be?
using the victim
you
Wonbin is the head of the division.
I want to file a complaint with the ethics committee.
Did you know? Didn't you know?
I knew it
But were you watching that?
what did i do for you
How dare you act like this
Put a knife in my back?
To be precise
It's not the managing director, it's the general manager.
Managing director too
That this is wrong
You know it well.
Now you see, what about you?
All I knew was
No, you encouraged it?
I was in a lot of pain too
I respected you, Mr.
To the managing director more than anyone else
Because I wanted to be recognized
But this isn't it
Taking advantage of the innocent victim
How can you even frame someone?
No matter how unpleasant No PD is,
Isn't this right?
hey! Jo Na-jeong!
something solid
I guess I'm mistaken.
The innocent person is not Wonbin
I'm the head of the department.
Yena wasn't manipulated
I'm just revealing the truth
But...
I have a question for you.
What is it?
Why did you like me?
Hey, shame on you
Do you really have to say it in words?
Uh, should I say it in words?
Was it just good?
Or was it Phil?
Of course there is Phil too.
And the more I look, the more I see
The charm explodes
Both...
Well, my brother usually
What type of woman are you attracted to?
Hmm... I haven't really thought about it like that.
Why? You told Jooyoung about it back then.
I like a cheerful and confident style.
Also, I don’t like being too immature.
Oh, that's right
I like that style
Independent and confident style
Then...
That woman too
Was it a bit like that?
That girl?
- who?
- That...
The doctor I met for 3 years...
No...
It's just the style you like
What do we have in common...
I see...
When I think about it
I think it was like that, a bit...
Really?
It won't be easy
Pleasant and confident
To even be considerate...
Is she married?
why? Are you curious?
I'm just asking
My brother knows about my
Because I don't know anything
It's a bit... unfair.
I haven't done it yet
I don't know why or why
Hey
Nothing to worry about, eh?
What do you mean? I'm worried
Let's just have fun
I'm just saying, let's have fun.
Well, because you pretend to be jealous
I think you're really jealous
Is that right?
I'm going to go to the bathroom for a moment.
Ha...
I'm worried and upset about my appearance...
What are you doing?
Hey...
Mr. Illy Lee
What are you doing now?
Are you spying now?
Are you jealous?
What is it, huh?
What are you so curious about?
I'll show you
What are you curious about? let's see
This?
Advertisement, today's restaurant
Huh? Tour, here is your top pick!
Did you want to see this?
What else? Jongseok?
Where are you?
Would you like to come have a drink with Hyeong-guk?
Right now, in front of the hospital
It’s a Mungtigi house.
Yes!
I'm jealous
I'm so jealous I'm dying
I'm like that girl
It's not a great job
Have you met my brother?
It wasn't much
I know, I'm a loser too.
Ah, this
It's so cute, this is it? uh?
I have this in my pocket
I can't carry it around
Oh, what!
I feel bad
Hey...
That's a confession
confession that I like it
Thank you, Elijah
For making me jealous
Until now I
I'm the only one who likes you
You are not my star
I don't think I like it
I was anxious
I'll bet, huh?
never in the future
I won't make you jealous
Uh, promise!
That's it!
Go away, go there
Why are you bothering me by sitting next to me?
- Hey, wow, does it hurt?
- Go over there.
- It's still the same.
- Go away.
I should have a drink here
Ta-da!
Mr...
Love shot?
Hey, hey, hey!
What are the rumors going around right now?
What rumor?
No, now people
I'm so scared
Your husband is the head of the department
He said he filed a complaint with the ethics committee.
But why
You cheated on me
Are you saying it's a trick to cover up?
Humans?
Ha...
What?
These are real human horses.
No, how can you manipulate the victim?
Are you thinking of framing me?
Song Yena, she...
Just...
Could he...
Managing Director Seo Prime Time
gives so
Didn't you just get away with it?
What does that mean?
no, i did this morning
Looking at the schedule
What I thought was strange
Song Yena, she
As prime time main show host
It's up
So, no, I
How did he get this position?
I was thinking about that
Really?
you look at this
Look at this
Ha...
Oh, what should I do with this?
How do I reveal that my name was framed?
Wait a minute
Why?
There's a saying like that
Even if there is a guy who doesn't cheat
There's no one who smokes only once
Why are you so obsessed with women?
Those with habits
I can't teach you my bad habits.
Then
Surely the victim
Two?
That's right
Uh, uh, Seonyoung, it’s me.
Do you have time with Minjoo?
Not yet
We also heard rumors
I thought everyone was shocked and passed by.
We don't even know that
With Seonmin and PD Noh
I thought it was an affair
So now
To clear No PD’s name
Chief, we must find other evidence.
Maybe the head of the department
Another female employee
Have you ever seen something gathering together?
I heard a rumor like that
Have you ever been like that?
Or something
Even if it’s just a passing comment?
I don't know
Oh, that's right
Not this one from the general manager before.
When you are in the support business team
Are you an intern?
A friend who seems to be a subordinate
I said I quit after 3 months.
- Really?
- But
I didn’t even submit a resignation letter, just
Because it didn’t come out right away
I heard you were criticized a lot.
Maybe...
Oh my!
It could be so.
Continue with your business support team
We became friends through skinship.
I know it's difficult
Can you give me your phone number?
It's because I'm so desperate
You know, Taejeong?
Oh, I understand.
But I recognized it.
What about this kind of thing?
Don't ever do it.
Uh, well, then
Uh, valet, valet, valet!
Oh, it's me
Before that, to the support business team
Among the interns who came in
3 months after coming in
You had a friend who went out
Ugh! Bitna Kim
Uh, give me that friend's number.
Can you tell?
Oh, why? That friend at that time
I'm good at work
I think there was a rumor
My friend has a part-time job
I need it urgently so
Ah...
Yeah?
Uh, okay then
Yeah
Why?
That friend... then
I heard you went to study abroad right after you quit your job?
okay?
What?
Asking about the last time
I'm reluctant to do so
I'm reporting this to the managing director.
I want to know because of my part-time job.
They said they said something
Because you never know
Okay
Thanks for letting me know
Ha...
Uh, Managing Director Seo.
I am a river
No, Chen Chen
It has the same composition as ours.
You're selling it for 189,000 won now?
Then it's ours
Aren’t they all going to be returned?
Let’s get off too
Shouldn't I sell it?
Uh... really?
Then...
Boss Kang
That
Other than me yet
You didn't tell anyone, right?
Yeah, why?
Then...
Just one time
I wish I could help you
What you ordered has arrived
thank you
What is it
I said I didn't add syrup.
If you buy a cake
What should I do to gain weight?
What did I say?
you are so skinny
I need to gain some weight
Hey, let's do it this way
I think it will fly away when the wind blows
Would you live with anxiety?
What, really!
Pure lie!
Stop looking at it, it's wearing out.
It's nice to see, right?
uh?
Mr. Illy Lee
When did that happen
Was it pretty?
Why are you like this, really!
When did that become popular?
Hey, look at that baby, he
Hey, it's so pretty
No, why is she so pretty?
- How old are you?
- Two years old.
Hey, if there's a girl that pretty like that
I'll be full even if I don't eat
Right?
Oh my...
Oh my, it looks like a doll, huh?
those dolls
What the master thinks
They're not those weird dolls.
Those dolls...
- When he was young!
- Mom, stop!
In this case
It's called paraphilia
I can't be certain
That's all with people
If communication is not possible
I'm an object lover
I can talk but
The patient is also married.
In the early days of newlyweds
I heard you also had a marital relationship.
That's right
Um...well, in the other direction.
You might need to think about it.
Even ordinary people
lightly on things
You can also personify it.
Some people in their cars
I also give it a nickname
People who play musical instruments
on your violin or cello
Sometimes we talk as if it's a joke
Ah...
Maybe in childhood
Have you been seriously hurt?
Or there is trauma
Haven't you heard anything?
I don't know
Now, finally
I'll check it out
She's Elegance Aluminum
Set of 5 99% pure frying pans
The price is 199,000 won.
Please tell us your selling point
The part about it being a collectible and not a consumable.
It has the same effect as a cast iron pan.
Due to the plasma method
High thermal conductivity
It has the advantage of not sticking.
Okay, good.
And finally
As a free gift, a bear pot that doubles as a steamer
Contains 15 Samgye chickens
Don't forget
Now then, let’s all fight!
- Fighting.
- Yes!
- Please take care of me.
- Yes
Yes, boss
Isn’t the observation staff coming today?
No PD
I have now obtained information about Chen Chen.
It has the same composition as ours.
They say they’ll sell it for 189,000 won?
yes?
Then it's ours
Not everything will be returned
Because I received confirmation from Managing Director Seo.
Let’s lower the price to 179,000 won and sell it.
Then the risk
Don't you think it's too big?
no, what
But what can I do?
Return came in
It's better than stockpiling
Ah... no matter what
It's too late to just proceed
It seems a bit dangerous.
I told Managing Director Seo and MD Choi
check it out
I'll call you back
Okay then
yes
The power is off
After the 'beep' sound...
your
My phone is off...
What is it?
Uh, did you check?
Ah, yes, boss.
Now, Director Seo and MD Choi
I didn't answer the phone.
First, I found the managing director.
Check it out...
No, what do you mean?
There are only 5 minutes left in the broadcast.
What else do you want to check?
Oh, I'm with Managing Director Seo.
I said everything was said.
What's so suspicious?
PD, what are you doing?
Aren't you coming in?
Just a moment, boss.
Hey, Hyungi.
You should call MD Choi.
If you get it, please change it for me
Yes, boss
But maybe
When are you meeting with Managing Director Seo?
Did you talk?
Just a moment ago
I heard you talked face to face
I'm not answering the phone
PD, you need to go in now.
It’s 3 minutes before the broadcast!
Yes, boss.
Are you sure?
Managing Director Seo confirmed it, right?
That's right
Ah, was this person just fooled?
yes, i understand
Then, we will adjust the price.
To the managing director, the boss is
Please explain the situation one more time
yes
Hey, Hyun-gi, the assistant control room is
I'll go and tell you
You go to the show hosts.
to 179,000 won
Please tell me you will adjust the price
Hey, and while it's on air
Call MD Choi
With Boss Kang
Let's negotiate later
yes, i understand
Come back
thank you
We prepared the third batch of 5,000 sets
The news is that everything is sold out.
Okay, if you missed it.
Don't be sorry
More meaningful in the next broadcast
We'll greet you with benefits
Thank you for being with us so far
Thank you
I was the show host Hong Seon-young.
I was the former show host Jo Na-jeong.
- Thank you
Cut!
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your hard work, yes.
- Good job.
- Yes
Thank you for your hard work, yes
yes, yes
Ah... yes
Thank you both for your hard work
It was a sudden situation
Don't be embarrassed
You handled it well too.
Thank you for your hard work
- Let's go eat.
- Oh, then.
- Wait a minute.
- Yes
Yes, Managing Director
What are you doing?
Why do you do what you want
Are you broadcasting by lowering the price?
yes?
No, what do you mean?
What the managing director confirmed
Wasn't it?
I?
Boss Kang
The managing director confirmed it.
You asked me to adjust the price.
what now
Are you talking nonsense?
When do I
Did you confirm something like that?
I?
When did I?
The boss told me
You said it clearly.
Because I received confirmation from the managing director.
Lower the price and proceed.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Checking competitor prices
I asked if that was true.
They said it was confirmed!
No, you are the boss now.
What are you talking about?
The boss
I met with the manager
I received confirmation after seeing my face.
clearly to me
You said so.
I am on this broadcast
I said I should never fail.
Can’t you trust people?
You were rude, you!
I confirmed it so don't bother me
I told you not to, you!
When did I do that, boss!
Why do you keep saying things that don’t exist?
Are you doing it?
under! I really
wise
What do you think?
Is it true what No PD said?
How much did you hear?
I don't know
I couldn't hear you very well
Hey
You sound like I'm talking on the phone
You heard it all
I was also busy preparing for the broadcast.
Because I didn't hear it correctly
- It's a bit hard to say for sure...
- Hyeongi.
Why are you like this now?
I... perhaps
Has anyone heard this?
under! I...
Who should take responsibility for whom now?
The amount of damage we saw
Do you know how much it is?
It's like 100 million, 100 million!
Ask me, right now
Ask for 100 million of my money!
Ask me, you bastard!
calm down
What the hell to me
Why are you doing this, yes?
Why are you being falsely accused like this?
Are you trying to cover it up?
To me
What kind of resentment is there!
president!
Hey, that guy is hitting people.
Hit the person, is that?
-Are you okay?
- Hey
Just one producer, a babbler
What about the CEO of a partner company? Assault?
Oh, me, hey
Don't do it, okay?
How are you going to take responsibility?
The damage caused to the company is also serious.
Assaulting the CEO of a partner company?
This is a home shopping abuse issue.
spreadable
You know this is a serious matter, right?
It's not assault
The first one to grab him by the collar was President Kang.
You've seen it all, Mr.
Who caught it first?
It's not important
Home shopping PD
The representative of the partner company said that
Dealing with it itself is a problem!
Above all, because of your mistake
We are over 100 million
I suffered a financial loss
A problem I can solve
I don't think so
It's not my mistake
President Kang told me
I lied.
No, that person
Why do you do that to me...
Maybe this
Did the managing director order you to do this?
What does that mean?
I am the head of the ethics committee.
Because of reporting
Did you set a trap on purpose?
I'm asking
you are doing it now
Are you doubting me too?
That's right
Because they framed me
You're trying to kick me out.
No?
here
Get someone out of my office
What are you doing now?
Managing Director, what are you doing now?
What are you doing right now?
You have to answer me.
Managing Director!
Handling it this way
Where are you?
Let go! Managing Director!
Managing Director!
I don’t have any pictures of me when I was young.
Are you at home?
hello
Guys
How are you?
That day...
my mom like that
For being rude
I'm so sorry
No, I'm more sorry
The reason I couldn’t prevent that situation
I'm more sorry
you and my parents
Who will suffer?
If you think about it
Don’t we have a lot in common?
He said he was also a mother and father.
A heavenly model student who could not disobey
I also couldn't say anything when my mom said it.
stupid schoolboy
Those model students
Even divorce is not easy.
that day
For the first time in my life, I told my mother
no more in my life
I told them not to get involved.
In the past, if you disobeyed your mother,
I thought the world would fall apart
What?
I felt so refreshed
Then I realized
Ah...
Even if I marry you
She was still just her mother's eldest daughter.
She wasn't your wife.
me
Let's have a child
Something that has been bothering you for a long time
I'm sorry
Why did I want to have a child?
Did I really want children?
I thought about it carefully.
To my mother
A good daughter giving her grandchildren
Being loved by my mother-in-law
I wanted to be a daughter-in-law
I really wanted to have a child
I don't think it was
That damn thing
Good kid complex
my life with you
It was eating away
But
I have one question
Yeah, what?
What my mother wanted to say that day
What does that mean?
Can you talk to me?
I'm sorry, Najeong.
I didn't even notice this obvious trap
Like a fool
It's all my fault
It's because I'm incompetent
It's all because I'm foolish
Lift your head up
Don't be weak
Lift your head upright
this time
It's not your fault
Even you incompetent people
I'm not a foolish person
Those people are evil
We never did anything wrong
Why don't you fight
It's so droopy!
Listen carefully
no matter what happens to me
I'm going to clear my name
I'm going to make all those bastards get punished.
Don't be weak
Just think about getting it right
Okay?
Don't worry, have a nice trip
I told the boss
I have something to say.
That somehow happened
I'll solve it
Why don't you just cut that guy?
I'm just ordering the left one, huh?
Late night early morning broadcast
Are you telling me to do it all in quick succession?
If you are not capable
Don't act like a fool and get out
Do you know your mother?
What kind of doll is that?
- Mom!
- Come here! Mr.
Jooyoung-ah, I’m sorry.
Then, when you get married
Do you want to have a baby?
Of course, I look like you
I wish I had a daughter
Not a rule, not a rule
Why are you bouncing like this, Mr.
Take everything you get, Mr.
Yena, please talk to me.
Should I talk in front of people?
Is that okay?